[
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Unearned Passenger Ticket Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Unearned Rental Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Anda tertangkap basah menerima gratifikasi dari pelanggan, dikenakan sanksi mundur 19 langkah.",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -19,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Allowance of Doubtful Accounts",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Mortgage Payable",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Dividend Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Share Capital - Ordinary",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Anda mendapatkan bonus dari pimpinan, diberikan hadiah untuk maju 7 langkah. ",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 7,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Dividend Receivable",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Share Capital - Premium",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  }
]
